

# Patryk Bejcer

Front-end Developer

#### **About me**

I am an experienced Frontend Developer with a focus on crafting dynamic interfaces using Vue.js. My expertise extends to PHP and Laravel, complemented by a wealth of knowledge in internet systems gained during my computer science studies. With a passion for creating intuitive and efficient solutions, I've been actively involved in the industry for eight years.

### **Contact Me**

- +48 696 755 343
- patryk.bejcer@gmail.com
- www.patrykbejcer.com.pl
- in www.linkedin.com/in/patryk-bejcer
- https://github.com/patryk-bejcer
- Głuchołazy, Opolskie 48-340

## Skills & Technologies

- Vue.js
- Nuxt.js
- Javascript
- HTML
- CSS (SCSS & SASS)
- Typescript
- Tailwind.css
- Wordpress
- React
- Base of Angular
- English (B1+)

- Laravel
- MySQL
- PHP
- Storybook
- GIT
- Rest API
- Figma
- Photoshop
- Jira & Clickup
- Vuetify

## **Work Experience**

Full-stack Developer
Massive Pixel Creation | 2018-present

#### Zendo (2020-2024)

As a Front-End Developer at Zendo, my focus was on utilizing technologies such as Vue, Nuxt, JavaScript, TypeScript, Tailwind.css, CSS, SCSS, and Webpack. I was responsible for developing the front-end layer and implementing key functionalities of the platform. Actively utilizing tools like Postman for function testing and Storybook for component documentation, these three years have been the highlight of my career. I learned a great deal during this time, contributing to my growth in the field of front-end development.

#### **Placester 2018-2020**

I contributed to a project for Placester.com, one of the prominent players in the real estate industry in the United States. The tech stack included PHP 7.1 with OOP, JS, MySQL, SCSS, and Angular. Additionally, I worked with various smaller clients, utilizing technologies such as WordPress, Vue, PHP, and web development for crafting tailored websites.

Full-stack DeveloperLumi Technology | 2015-2018

Work on projects for clients from England, Germany, and Poland. In this role, I was involved in the development of web applications based on the Laravel framework and the creation of themes for the WordPress CMS. Additionally, I worked with platforms such as Drupal, and October CMS. This position marked my first foray into commercial experience, concurrent with my studies in IT.

#### **Education**

2015 - 2019

Państwowa Akademia Nauk Stosowanych w Nysie

Engineer's degree, Information Technology

2010 - 2014

Zespół Szkół w Głuchołazach

IT specialist, Technical